<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Features on</title><link>https://moneymanagerex.org/docs/features/</link><description>Recent content in Features on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://moneymanagerex.org/docs/features/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Accounts &amp; Currencies</title><link>https://moneymanagerex.org/docs/features/accounts/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://moneymanagerex.org/docs/features/accounts/</guid><description>Money Manager EX allows you to create new bank accounts easily with a simple wizard. It currently supports three types of accounts:
Types of Accounts # Checking Account # Description: The most common type of account in MMEX. Usage: Suitable for checking accounts, savings accounts, and credit card accounts. Transactions: Supports withdrawals, deposits, and transfers. Alias: Also known as Bank Account. Term Account # Description: Similar to Checking Accounts but with the option to show or hide them for daily usage.</description></item><item><title>Transactions</title><link>https://moneymanagerex.org/docs/features/transactions/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://moneymanagerex.org/docs/features/transactions/</guid><description>Money Manager EX allows tracking incomes and expenses inserting new transactions for every money movement.
Transactions are divided for each bank account and they could have different status:
Unreconciled: When you enter a transaction, it initially is in the state of &amp;ldquo;Unreconciled&amp;rdquo;. Which means the transaction has not been reconciled with your bank/credit card company&amp;rsquo;s balance.
Reconciled: Once the transaction is checked and verified with a credit card company&amp;rsquo;s balance information, it can be marked as reconciled.</description></item><item><title>Payees &amp; Categories</title><link>https://moneymanagerex.org/docs/features/payees/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://moneymanagerex.org/docs/features/payees/</guid><description>Money Manager EX allows assigning to every transaction a payee and one or more categories.
Payees are the people or institutions that give us money, or the people or institutions that we pay, for our goods and services. It&amp;rsquo;s possible to associate a specific category with the payee, in this way it&amp;rsquo;s possible to have the category pre-loaded when inserting new transactions.
A Category is generally used to record Income or Expenses.</description></item><item><title>Scheduled Transactions</title><link>https://moneymanagerex.org/docs/features/scheduled/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://moneymanagerex.org/docs/features/scheduled/</guid><description>Money Manager EX allows creating scheduled transactions to track financial activities that occur at once or at regular intervals, such as the payment of a bill or a monthly mortgage.
When one or more schedules are enabled, transactions will be created in your account as by schedules. They are also needed to create cash flow reports with the number of funds available, based on future commitments.
These special transactions:
Are displayed as reminders on the Dashboard within 15 days of the due date Can be set up to activate automatically on the due date Can be set up to activate allowing the user to adjust any values on the due date It’s possible to achieve a high level of schedule customization:</description></item><item><title>Stocks &amp; Shares</title><link>https://moneymanagerex.org/docs/features/stocks/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://moneymanagerex.org/docs/features/stocks/</guid><description>Money Manager Ex allows the tracking of stocks and shares to be incorporated with our general day-to-day transactions. Stock holdings have been updated to allow money from our general accounts to be transferred to and from our investment accounts. This also allows the payment of dividends to be recorded against our stock holdings. To facilitate this, a share account is created when we add a new stock (would re-use the investment account).</description></item><item><title>Assets</title><link>https://moneymanagerex.org/docs/features/assets/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://moneymanagerex.org/docs/features/assets/</guid><description>Money Manager EX allows tracking fixed assets like cars, houses, land, and others.
Each asset can have its value appreciate by a certain rate per year, depreciate by a certain rate per year, or not change in value. The total assets are added to your total financial worth.</description></item><item><title>Budgeting</title><link>https://moneymanagerex.org/docs/features/budgeting/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://moneymanagerex.org/docs/features/budgeting/</guid><description>Money Manager EX allows you to set up a budget for a year and/or a month.
In this way, it&amp;rsquo;s possible to compare the money spent versus the actual budget. Budgets can be displayed in calendar years or financial years, depending on the setting chosen.</description></item><item><title>Attachments</title><link>https://moneymanagerex.org/docs/features/attachments/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://moneymanagerex.org/docs/features/attachments/</guid><description>Money Manager EX allows adding every file as an attachment for one of its elements (like transactions, accounts, assets, etc..)
All attachments are copied into a user-defined folder and not simply linked to the original file: in this way, they will remain accessible also if the original files are removed and it&amp;rsquo;s possible to backup all of them by simply copying the entire folder.
Bring Your Own Cloud could synchronize these attachments and database files across all your devices,</description></item><item><title>General Reports</title><link>https://moneymanagerex.org/docs/features/generalreports/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://moneymanagerex.org/docs/features/generalreports/</guid><description>Money Manager EX allows to create custom and heavy personalized report without external tools but using an internal templating engine.
It&amp;rsquo;s possible to obtain a report that suits to a T with:
SQL queries to obtain needed data from the database LUA code to modify and add some logic to the selected date HTML/CSS/JS to show data with preferred style We have created a repository on Github and a forum section with lots of examples and discussions on how to develop and improve them.</description></item><item><title>Import &amp; export</title><link>https://moneymanagerex.org/docs/features/importexport/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://moneymanagerex.org/docs/features/importexport/</guid><description>Money Manager EX allows to import and export data from different file types.
Supported formats are:
QIF (Quicken Interchange Format) CSV (Comma-Separated Values) HTML (HyperText Markup Language) XML (Extensible Markup Language) To alleviate the problem of users having to pre-format their bank transaction CSV files into the fixed format that software requires, MMEX allows users to import CSV files where the order of fields is completely freeform. To use this importer, select the order of fields in the CSV file by picking and choosing from the list of possible fields.</description></item></channel></rss>