<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blog on</title><link>https://moneymanagerex.org/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blog on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://moneymanagerex.org/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>MMEX Cloud Storage with NextCloud</title><link>https://moneymanagerex.org/blog/mmex-cloud-storage-with-nextcloud/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://moneymanagerex.org/blog/mmex-cloud-storage-with-nextcloud/</guid><description>Money Manager EX supports Bring Your Own Cloud, and this article provides a detailed guide on setting up MMEX with NextCloud for data sharing on your Android device.
Preparation # You&amp;rsquo;ll need a device running Android 5.1 or newer and a NextCloud account.
Install NextCloud # Install the NextCloud app on your device from your preferred source or directly from the NextCloud GitHub. Ensure you have NextCloud app version: v3.</description></item><item><title>MMEX Cloud Storage with Synology Drive</title><link>https://moneymanagerex.org/blog/mmex-cloud-storage-with-synology-drive/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://moneymanagerex.org/blog/mmex-cloud-storage-with-synology-drive/</guid><description>Money Manager EX supports Bring Your Own Cloud, and this article provides a detailed guide on setting up MMEX with Synology Drive for data sharing on your Android device.
Preparation # You&amp;rsquo;ll need a device running Android 5.1 or newer and a cloud provider account. In this guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll use Synology Drive.
Install Synology Drive # Install the Synology Drive app on your device from your preferred source or directly from the Synology Download Center.</description></item><item><title>Assets - a worked example</title><link>https://moneymanagerex.org/blog/assets-a-worked-example/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://moneymanagerex.org/blog/assets-a-worked-example/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve used bank accounts, credit card accounts and term accounts, transactions, and payees in mmex for many years now, previously on Windows and now on Linux (mmex v1.7.0), and am very happy with it - huge thanks from me to all the developers!
Occasionally I would try and use assets and asset accounts but always got confused and gave up.
This time I am determined to succeed, and wish there was a worked example (or even a tutorial) to help.</description></item><item><title>What's behind the increase in release</title><link>https://moneymanagerex.org/blog/whats-behind-the-increase-in-release/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://moneymanagerex.org/blog/whats-behind-the-increase-in-release/</guid><description>Money Manager Ex offered a new release every 2-6 weeks since April 2021. What&amp;rsquo;s behind the increase in releases?
&amp;ldquo;Frequent releases lets users see that the software is actively developed,&amp;rdquo; says developer Mark Whalley. &amp;ldquo;It gives them confidence in the software.&amp;rdquo; Mark made his first contribution to Money Manager Ex in November 2020. Since then he quickly became one of the top developers for Money Manager Ex. He&amp;rsquo;s made changes to the code almost every day this year and manages releases for macOS.</description></item><item><title>Explanation on Downtime</title><link>https://moneymanagerex.org/blog/explanation-on-downtime/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://moneymanagerex.org/blog/explanation-on-downtime/</guid><description>All MMEX users,
Just a short explanation of what happened. Basically, these several hours down was due to the php7.3-fpm down due to some unknown issues. Just restart the service to fix it and will keep an eye on this.
mmex@vps:~$ sudo service php7.3-fpm status ● php7.3-fpm.service - The PHP 7.3 FastCGI Process Manager Loaded: loaded (/lib/systemd/system/php7.3-fpm.service; enabled; vendor preset: enabled) Active: failed (Result: timeout) since Fri 2020-10-30 01:41:02 EDT; 2min 8s ago Docs: man:php-fpm7.</description></item></channel></rss>