<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blog on</title><link>https://moneymanagerex.org/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blog on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://moneymanagerex.org/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How to read Balance in single-account panels</title><link>https://moneymanagerex.org/blog/how-to-read-balance-in-single-account-panels/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://moneymanagerex.org/blog/how-to-read-balance-in-single-account-panels/</guid><description>In single-account panels, column Balance shows the account balance after the execution of each transaction.
Short description (what you see in GUI) # In 1.9.0, Balance is calculated in the order of SN (Sequence Number).
To read Balance in the correct (calculation) order, you should sort by SN in ascending order, i.e., if the current sorting column is anything else, just click once on the SN header.
Sorting by SN shows Balance in calculation order also when scheduled transactions are enabled (with the square button next to the filter selector).</description></item><item><title>MMEX Stock v2 - Preview and Changes</title><link>https://moneymanagerex.org/blog/mmex-stock-v2-preview-and-changes/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://moneymanagerex.org/blog/mmex-stock-v2-preview-and-changes/</guid><description>Overview # MMEX Stock v2 brings significant improvements to how investment accounts and stock trading are managed. This update enhances financial tracking by introducing a new cash ledger system, refining trade transactions, and deprecating outdated concepts. Below are the key changes:
Key Changes in MMEX Stock v2 # 1. Deprecation of Shares Account # Previously, MMEX used a Shares Account to handle cash transactions related to stock investments. This approach linked stock transactions to cash in a somewhat tricky manner, requiring additional manual tracking.</description></item><item><title>MMEX Asset Purchase - A Worked Example</title><link>https://moneymanagerex.org/blog/mmex-asset-purchase-a-worked-example/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://moneymanagerex.org/blog/mmex-asset-purchase-a-worked-example/</guid><description>.scroll-container { display: flex; overflow-x: auto; gap: 10px; white-space: nowrap; padding-bottom: 10px; } .scroll-container img { max-height: 600px; flex-shrink: 0; } This guide provides a detailed example of how to record an asset purchase in MMEX, from initial setup to tracking value changes over time.
In the Real World - The Purchase # I bought a property for £100,000 on 21 June 2000 as a cash buyer. The legal fees for the purchase were £1,000.</description></item><item><title>Sync MMEX iOS and Mac via iCloud</title><link>https://moneymanagerex.org/blog/sync-mmex-ios-and-mac-via-icloud/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://moneymanagerex.org/blog/sync-mmex-ios-and-mac-via-icloud/</guid><description>We’re excited to announce the integration of MMEX on iOS and Mac via iCloud, enabling you to sync your MMEX data effortlessly between devices. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re managing finances on your iPhone or Mac, this seamless sync ensures that your data stays up-to-date across both devices.
Follow this guide to sync your MMEX data between iOS and Mac using iCloud.
Preparation # Install MMEX on both your iPhone (version 0.1.28) and Mac (version 1.</description></item><item><title>Integrate SQLite3MC into MMEX iOS Project</title><link>https://moneymanagerex.org/blog/integrate-sqlite3mc-into-mmex-ios-project/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://moneymanagerex.org/blog/integrate-sqlite3mc-into-mmex-ios-project/</guid><description>Introduction # This guide outlines the process of integrating SQLite3MultipleCiphers (SQLite3MC) into the MMEX iOS project. SQLite3MC provides support for multiple encryption algorithms, enhancing SQLite database security. The SQLCipher legacy v4 cipher is fully compatible with other MMEX platforms (Desktop and Android), SQLCipher from Zetetic, and wxSQLitePlus.
Steps to Integrate SQLite3MC # Follow these steps to add SQLite3MC to your MMEX project:
Step 1: Add SQLite3MC Source Files # Download the SQLite3MC source code from its official repository.</description></item><item><title>Connect iOS and Android MMEX with Synology Drive</title><link>https://moneymanagerex.org/blog/connect-ios-and-android-mmex-with-synology-drive/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://moneymanagerex.org/blog/connect-ios-and-android-mmex-with-synology-drive/</guid><description>With the valuable support of both Guangong and George Ef, we have launched the beta version of MMEX for iOS. We invite you to join our beta testing via TestFlight.
In this guide, we will explain how to sync your MMEX database between your iOS and Android devices.
Preparation # Set up MMEX on your Android device by following MMEX Cloud Storage with Synology Drive. Install Synology Drive and the latest version of MMEX4iOS on your iOS device.</description></item><item><title>MMEX Database Sync Across Android, iOS, and Desktop</title><link>https://moneymanagerex.org/blog/mmex-database-sync-across-android-ios-and-desktop/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://moneymanagerex.org/blog/mmex-database-sync-across-android-ios-and-desktop/</guid><description>Managing and syncing an SQLite database across different platforms is crucial for ensuring data integrity, especially when working with personal finance apps like Money Manager EX (MMEX). This article details the approaches MMEX takes to use and sync the underlying SQLite database across Android, iOS, and Desktop platforms. Understanding these strategies will help you effectively manage your database and avoid conflicts when accessing data from multiple devices.
Platform Comparison for SQLite Database Syncing in MMEX # Here’s a table comparing the approach MMEX uses to sync the SQLite database across Android, iOS, and Desktop:</description></item><item><title>MMEX Android Attachment Preview Support</title><link>https://moneymanagerex.org/blog/mmex-android-attachment-preview-support/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://moneymanagerex.org/blog/mmex-android-attachment-preview-support/</guid><description>Money Manager EX (MMEX) for Android now includes attachment preview support, allowing users to view files like receipts and invoices linked to their transactions. This feature builds on MMEX’s existing attachment support for desktops, as detailed in the MMEX Desktop Attachment Guide. Here’s a step-by-step guide to configuring attachment previews in MMEX4Android.
Setting Up the Attachment Folder # To enable attachment previews, you’ll first need to configure the folder where MMEX accesses and stores attachments.</description></item><item><title>MMEX Cloud Storage with NextCloud</title><link>https://moneymanagerex.org/blog/mmex-cloud-storage-with-nextcloud/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://moneymanagerex.org/blog/mmex-cloud-storage-with-nextcloud/</guid><description>Money Manager EX supports Bring Your Own Cloud, and this article provides a detailed guide on setting up MMEX with NextCloud for data sharing on your Android device.
Preparation # You&amp;rsquo;ll need a device running Android 5.1 or newer and a NextCloud account.
Install NextCloud # Install the NextCloud app on your device from your preferred source or directly from the NextCloud GitHub. Ensure you have NextCloud app version: v3.</description></item><item><title>MMEX Cloud Storage with Synology Drive</title><link>https://moneymanagerex.org/blog/mmex-cloud-storage-with-synology-drive/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://moneymanagerex.org/blog/mmex-cloud-storage-with-synology-drive/</guid><description>Money Manager EX supports Bring Your Own Cloud, and this article provides a detailed guide on setting up MMEX with Synology Drive for data sharing on your Android device.
Preparation # You&amp;rsquo;ll need a device running Android 5.1 or newer and a cloud provider account. In this guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll use Synology Drive.
Install Synology Drive # Install the Synology Drive app on your device from your preferred source or directly from the Synology Download Center.</description></item></channel></rss>