<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>MMEX on</title><link>https://www.moneymangerex.org/docs/mmex/</link><description>Recent content in MMEX on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.moneymangerex.org/docs/mmex/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Contributors</title><link>https://www.moneymangerex.org/docs/mmex/contributors/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.moneymangerex.org/docs/mmex/contributors/</guid><description> Active Developers # Nikolay Whalley Gabriele Lisheng James Stefano Pat Translations # Albanian Artur Gjevori Brazilian Portuguese Jose Carlos, Daniel Cunha de Almeida Bulgarian Ivan Gyokov, Poltargaista Croatian Goran Bobanovic Czech Josef Remes, PepaR Dutch Theo Kamphuis, PeCe Dutch (Belgian) Rol, wimvhs Englsh (UK) mcrossley French Berry As, Jean-Christophe, bipop, drambeau, Ben, Ghislain Baudichaud phira German Renato Schrempfi, goe, STiGMaTa_ch, Kai Kajus Noack Greek Panagiotis Pentzeridis Panagiotis Sapikas Polvar Hebrew Avi Markovitz Hungarian Csaba, Zoltan Levardy Toroka Hindi Ankur Jain Indonesian Dindin Italian Maurizio Claudio Lithuanian akmc Norwegian Fredrik Strand, Torbjorn Kvande Polish Damian_pl Andrzej Jerzy Machnicki Portuguese (Portugal) Fatela Romanian Munteanu &amp;amp; Florin Russian KarmaSV, Nikolay, Churzzz, Vadim Simple Chinese Liu Ming Slovak Abadyba, Misko B Spanish jorgeb Javier, Roberto Swedish tomastomas Traditional Chinese Kysouke Tamil Gopi Gopalakrishnan, Muguntharaj Subramanian Turkish Murat Bilgen Ukrainian Leonid Shturma Vietnamese Nicky, Luu Cong Thanh, Toan User Manual # English Stefano Tina P, Terry Wick Italian Maurizio French catacotox phira Gernam Renato Hungarian Toroka Russian Nikolay Polish Damian_pl Spanish jorgeb, kolmo7 Art and Icons # SVG Repo</description></item><item><title>Donate</title><link>https://www.moneymangerex.org/docs/mmex/donate/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.moneymangerex.org/docs/mmex/donate/</guid><description>There are different ways you can donate to the project&amp;hellip; # Help with the development # If you have experience and the time then why not contribute to the software development and maintenance, visit us on GitHub
Publish a review # Write an review on one or all of the the following sites.
sourceforge AlternativeTo Download.com Mac Update or post a review and link to us on
Facebook Twitter Record a review of help others # Why not record a review or a screencast to explain a features?</description></item><item><title>Downloads</title><link>https://www.moneymangerex.org/docs/mmex/downloads/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.moneymangerex.org/docs/mmex/downloads/</guid><description>Upgrading from v1.4.0? # If you get the database error, &amp;ldquo;MMEX database version 13 doesn&amp;rsquo;t work with this MMEX version,&amp;rdquo; then see Steps to convert your database from 1.4.x
The latest Money Manager Ex release uses the database structure of the 1.3.x series and discontinued the structure of version 1.4.x. This maintains compatibility with the mobile app.
Beta/Development Builds # Windows MacOS Title Paragraph Text</description></item><item><title>License</title><link>https://www.moneymangerex.org/docs/mmex/license/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.moneymangerex.org/docs/mmex/license/</guid><description>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE # Version 2, June 1991
Copyright (C) 1989, 1991 Free Software Foundation, Inc. 51 Franklin Street, Fifth Floor, Boston, MA 02110-1301, USA Everyone is permitted to copy and distribute verbatim copiesof this license document, but changing it is not allowed.
Preamble # The licenses for most software are designed to take away your freedom to share and change it. By contrast, the GNU General Public License is intended to guarantee your freedom to share and change free software&amp;ndash;to make sure the software is free for all its users.</description></item><item><title>Press Reviews</title><link>https://www.moneymangerex.org/docs/mmex/press/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.moneymangerex.org/docs/mmex/press/</guid><description>Money Manager Ex is a software for Windows that helps you manage your finances easily. You can manage your personal as well as business finances with this application. It is free-to-use software. This open-source and cross-platform finance software creates an overview of your financial worth. Simply put, Money Manager Ex primarily keeps a track of your money, like – when and how the money goes.
*Review by The Windows Club on 2018-08-24</description></item><item><title>Privacy</title><link>https://www.moneymangerex.org/docs/mmex/privacy/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.moneymangerex.org/docs/mmex/privacy/</guid><description>What information do we collect? # We collect information from you when you register on our site or subscribe to our newsletter.
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
What do we use your information for? # Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:</description></item></channel></rss>