<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>MMEX on</title><link>https://moneymanagerex.org/contributors/mmex/</link><description>Recent content in MMEX on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://moneymanagerex.org/contributors/mmex/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How to read Balance in single-account panels</title><link>https://moneymanagerex.org/blog/how-to-read-balance-in-single-account-panels/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://moneymanagerex.org/blog/how-to-read-balance-in-single-account-panels/</guid><description>In single-account panels, column Balance shows the account balance after the execution of each transaction.
Short description (what you see in GUI) # In 1.9.0, Balance is calculated in the order of SN (Sequence Number).
To read Balance in the correct (calculation) order, you should sort by SN in ascending order, i.e., if the current sorting column is anything else, just click once on the SN header.
Sorting by SN shows Balance in calculation order also when scheduled transactions are enabled (with the square button next to the filter selector).</description></item><item><title>MMEX Stock v2 - Preview and Changes</title><link>https://moneymanagerex.org/blog/mmex-stock-v2-preview-and-changes/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://moneymanagerex.org/blog/mmex-stock-v2-preview-and-changes/</guid><description>Overview # MMEX Stock v2 brings significant improvements to how investment accounts and stock trading are managed. This update enhances financial tracking by introducing a new cash ledger system, refining trade transactions, and deprecating outdated concepts. Below are the key changes:
Key Changes in MMEX Stock v2 # 1. Deprecation of Shares Account # Previously, MMEX used a Shares Account to handle cash transactions related to stock investments. This approach linked stock transactions to cash in a somewhat tricky manner, requiring additional manual tracking.</description></item><item><title>MMEX Asset Purchase - A Worked Example</title><link>https://moneymanagerex.org/blog/mmex-asset-purchase-a-worked-example/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://moneymanagerex.org/blog/mmex-asset-purchase-a-worked-example/</guid><description>.scroll-container { display: flex; overflow-x: auto; gap: 10px; white-space: nowrap; padding-bottom: 10px; } .scroll-container img { max-height: 600px; flex-shrink: 0; } This guide provides a detailed example of how to record an asset purchase in MMEX, from initial setup to tracking value changes over time.
In the Real World - The Purchase # I bought a property for £100,000 on 21 June 2000 as a cash buyer. The legal fees for the purchase were £1,000.</description></item></channel></rss>